bankexamportal.com 2013-03-15

# 

**Climb First – Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. 

When visiting our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: 

 Name, e-mail address, phone number and  the Course you are looking for.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; For Career Counseling  
(On receiving your information, we call you to help you better understand the course, the exam pattern, eligibility criteria etc. Along with that we also explain to you our modus – oprandi, how we would be coaching you and leading you to success.)

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

; To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information**?

Your information is completely for career counselling  once u with to opted out for will not contact your that information will be deleted permanently form system.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our 

[websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 4/11/2011

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

277 - 279, Powai Plaza, Powai  
Mumbai, Maharashtra 400076  
India  
climbfirst@gmail.com  
7738364800
